还有多远  爸爸
How much farther, Daddy?
我们之前在岔路转错弯了
Well, we, uh, took a wrong turn at the fork a ways back.
但现在走的路没错
But, uh, we're heading the right way now.
快到家了
We're almost home.
到家了我会很开心的
I'll be glad when we get there.
我也是
Yeah, me, too.
-爸爸  -没事
- Daddy? - It's okay.
迷路了吗
You lost?
我怕
I'm scared.
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
靠近我
Just stay close.
格雷西
Gracie?
Gracie!
格雷西
住手
Stop!
大伙
Dudes...
大伙  大伙
Dudes? Dudes!
有缺口  它们进来了
Breach! They're inside the wall!
有缺口
Breach!
拿上武器
Grab your weapons!
-爸爸  -有缺口
- Daddy? - There's a breach!
格雷西  我要你下楼
Hey, Gracie, uh, I need you to head downstairs
进地下室  别让任何人进去  好吗
into the basement and don't let anyone in, okay?
就像之前练过的一样
Just like we practiced, alright?
你待在里面  哨子带着吗
And you stay there, okay? You have your whistle?
好
Okay.
好  快去
Okay, go now.
修好墙
Get 'em back!
用横梁
Use the beams!
堵住洞
Fill the hole!
好了
That's it!
行尸走肉
第十一季  第五集
联邦
大家好
Hello!
兰斯·霍恩斯比
运营主管
我是兰斯·霍恩斯比
I'm Lance Hornsby.
欢迎来到联邦
Welcome to the Commonwealth.
联邦赢得您的信任
联邦之道
如果您正在观看这个录像  说明您通过了
If you're watching this video, you've made it through
联邦社区严格的审查过程
the rigorous screening process of the Commonwealth community
已获批准加入我们
and have been approved to join us.
在帕梅拉·弥尔顿总管的领导下
Under the leadership of Governor Pamela Milton,
我们已有五万多人
we are over 50,000 strong,
每个人都被专门分配
with every person specially assigned
和安排到了最适合其技能的岗位上
and curated to the job best suited to their skill set
以保证这个社区的蓬勃发展
to keep this community thriving.
本介绍将让您大致了解
This orientation will give you a taste
我们为您准备了些什么
of what we have in store for you.
未来始于这里
The future starts here.
社区
Community.
照料
Caregiving.
安全
Security.
保障您的安全
抗击死者
拯救生者
这就是"联邦之道"
That's "The Commonwealth Way."
帕梅拉·弥尔顿认可此信息
帕梅拉·弥尔顿
Pamela Milton?
尤金·伯特
"Eugene Porter.
岗位详情  高中教师团队
Work Detail -- high-school teaching pool.
住宿详情  1区13号房
Boarding Detail -- Bungalow 13, Sector 1..."
很好  好
Yes! Okay.
这是个好兆头
This is a good sign.
请原谅我问东问西
Pardon my gazing of a gift horse in the gullet,
但这些详情是什么意思
but what in the heck are these details meant to convey?
工作分配和住房
Job assignments and housing.
我们不打算在此永久居住
Permanent residency here was not our intent.
如果你有意见
If you have a problem with it,
去找个案监督员
take it up with the case supervisor.
等等  你们分了什么工作
Wait. What jobs did you guys get?
这不重要  我们不是来打工的
Doesn't matter. We're not here to work.
-我们是来求助的  -那当然
- We're here to get help. - Uh, totally.
我只是有点好奇  因为他们分我当导购
I-I was just curious 'cause they gave me "Retail clerk."
这让我怀疑这里是不是有商场
Made me wonder if they have a mall here,
如果有的话就太赞了
'cause that'd be frickin' amazing.
我以前超喜欢在商场工作
I used to love working in the mall.
他们分我去动物管理处
They put me in animal control.
我估计这些都基于灾变前的工作经历
I imagine all of these are based on jobs from before the fall.
我收到的不是岗位分配
Yeah, mine isn't really an assignment.
看起来像封邀请函
Looks like an invitation.
联邦事务办公室
亲爱的奥村女士
我们很希望见到您
并与您讨论在我们伟大社区内的机会
请您尽早到事务办公室报到
有人想见我  并谈谈  引用原话
Someone wants to meet and talk about, and I quote,
"我们伟大社区内的机会"
"Opportunities within our great community."
由美子真上流  肯定是因为口音
Ooh! Yumiko's fancy! Must be the accent.
我们必须立刻修正路线
We need to plot a course correction ASAP
以防琐事干扰主要计划
before these entanglements usurp our Plan A.
我认为应该采取多管齐下的策略
I think a multi-pronged strategy would be in order.
同意
Agreed.
我去看看个案监督员能做什么
I'll see what this case supervisor can do.
我和以西结一起去
Um, I'm gonna go with Ezekiel.
我想多见识一下这地方
I wanna see more of this place.
而且我感觉很走运
And I'm feeling lucky.
我定好要与史蒂芬妮见面
I'm supposed to meet up with Stephanie.
我会了解一下此地情况和内幕
I'll get the lay of the land and the proverbial skinny.
也许给你这个的人能帮到你
Maybe whoever gave you that can help.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你的个案监督员会回答你的一切问题
Your case supervisor can answer all your questions.
嗯  但我貌似没有监督员
Yeah, I don't seem to have one of those.
只有一封事务办公室给我发的函
Just this letter from the Office of State Affairs.
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
我能帮您什么忙
How can I help?
在评估期间
Well, during processing,
我问了我住在这里的亲人的情况
I was inquiring about a family member living here,
但一直没得到回复
but I haven't heard anything since.
我很乐意为您效劳
I'd be happy to help you with that.
行尸破墙而入过后  墙会更加不稳固
The wall's gonna be more fragile since they broke through.
大家越来越焦虑
People are getting anxious.
北边聚集了行尸
There's dead on the north side.
我们通过敲墙来分散它们  起作用了
We're banging the wall to spread them out. It's working.
暂时的而已  它们会回来的
For now, but they'll be back.
是啊  我们得彻底修好
Yeah, we need a long-term fix.
工具有什么新进展吗
Any update on tools?
被戴皮者毁坏的还没能补回来
Still haven't replaced what the skins destroyed.
而且我们的粮食又快吃完了
And we're back to square one on food.
剩下的马肉已经被腌上风干了
What's left of the horse has been salted and jerkied.
那玩意不好吃  但依旧消耗得很快
Stuff's nasty, but it's going fast.
山顶寨呢
What about Hilltop?
也许还有些打铁工具没被烧毁
Maybe some of the blacksmithing tools survived the fire.
我们几个人可以跑一趟
A few of us can make a run,
-沿途还可以看看有没有猎物  -好
- maybe see if there's some game nearby while we're at it. - Yeah.
如果什么都没了呢
And if there's nothing left?
如果我们没法保证亚历山大的安全
If we can't make Alexandria safe,
那我们就得开始考虑其他选项了
we need to start thinking about other options.
亚历山大是我们的家
Alexandria's our home.
我还没准备好抛弃它
I'm not ready to abandon ship.
现在还不行
Not yet.
我们得先努力拯救它
We gotta fight to save it first.
我们得走了
We should get moving.
其他人可能已经到哨站了
The others could already be at the outpost.
也可能只剩咱俩了
Or it could just be us.
你知道要想这次任务成功
You know the only way this works
我们必须相互信任吧
is if we trust each other.
我怎么可能信任你
Why would I ever trust you?
我不知道  玛姬
I don't know, Maggie.
也许是因为你想活下来  我也一样
'Cause you want to stay alive, same as me.
如果我活了下来
If I stay alive,
那也是因为没有你  而不是因为你
it'll be in spite of you, not because of you.
老天啊
Jesus.
如果你真这么觉得
You know, if -- if that's how you feel,
那我就不明白你为何还没干掉我了
I don't understand why you haven't put me down yet.
靠
Shit!
我每天都会问自己这个问题
I ask myself that question every day.
靠
Shit.
老天啊
Jesus.
快看
Look.
基本上已经被洗劫一空了
Practically been picked clean.
可能不只有行尸
Might be more than the dead.
当心
Heads up.
那些是我们的人
Those are our people.
哥们
Dude...
那是特洛伊
It's Troy.
快动手吧
Let's just get this done.
-我们得走了  -嗯
- We need to keep moving. - Yeah.
注意周围
Eyes open.
预备  开始
Ready? Start!
很好  再来
Good. Again.
保持中心姿态
Center yourself.
重心放在后脚
Weight on your back foot.
瞄准头部  刺
Aim for the head, then stab!
很好  再来
Good. Again.
看啊  太疯狂了
Look. This is crazy.
天啊
God.
怎么了
What's wrong?
你们不应该那么做
You shouldn't be doing that!
离开那里
Get away from there.
冷静  我们只是在闹着玩
Calm down. We're just having fun.
这很危险
It's dangerous.
如果你们不停下  我就去告诉罗西塔
If you don't stop, I'm gonna tell Rosita.
闭嘴  你话太多了
Shut up! You talk too much.
难怪你妈抛弃了你
No wonder your mom abandoned you.
你说什么
What did you say?
你真爱抱怨
You're such a baby.
她一定是厌倦了她整天叽叽歪歪的
She must've gotten tired of all her whining.
再说一遍
Say it again.
你敢不敢
I dare you.
朱迪思  别
Judith, don't.
离我远一点  你个变态
Stay away from me, you psycho.
看什么看
What are you looking at?
看上去不像是有人来过  所以说...
Doesn't look like anybody's been here, so...
所以我们等着
So we wait.
等多久
How long?
换做是你  你希望别人等你多久
How long would you want someone to wait for you?
我只是觉得我们在这里待得越久
I just think the longer we stay here,
就越有可能被那些疯子抓到
the more likely it is that these lunatics catch us.
不如我们带着这些食物回去吧
Look, how about we take this food back, alright?
虽然没多少
I know it's not a lot,
但也算是有所收获了
but at least it's something.
这根本不够
It's nothing.
我们得喂饱整个社区的人
We need to feed a whole community.
玛姬  你得学会及时放手
Maggie, you need to know when to cut your losses.
你所谓的放手...
Those losses...
是指抛下我的人
are my people.
我懂  我真的懂
I know. I do.
但你还有其他人
But you still have people.
你还有赫谢尔
You still have Hershel.
你以为我不明白这一点吗
Do you think I don't know that?
正因如此我们才要跑这一趟
It's the reason we're doing this.
但"我们"做不到
But "we" can't.
这就是我想说的
See, that's my point.
好吧  我知道我没有投票权
Alright, look, I-I know I don't get a vote here,
没关系  但不管怎样  这是我的提议
and that's fine, but here's mine anyway.
我们等到日落
We give it 'til sundown.
如果其他人到那时还没出现
And if the others don't show by then,
他们就不会再出现了
they're not gonna.
现烤派
每日供应
我马上就来
Um, I'll be right with you.
你好吗
Hi. How you doing?
甜甜圈刚刚出炉
Just got a fresh batch of doughnuts out of the oven.
其实我是来找人的
I-I'm actually looking for someone.
蛋糕上好糖霜了  老板
Cake's frosted and ready, boss.
我要不要送去...
Should I run it over to --
你好  托米
Hi, Tomi.
没剩多少了  但比没有强
Not much, but better than nothing.
我们拥有的一切都没了
Everything we have, gone.
不是一切
Not everything.
我们还活着很多人
A lot of us are still standing.
记住这一点
Remember that.
又来了
There's more.
我们搜寻前得把它们处理掉
We need to take care of it before we keep searching.
等等  看
Wait. Look.
它们移动的方式
The way they're moving...
它们在被驱赶
They're being herded.
低语者
Whisperers.
住手  别杀他
Stop! Don't kill him!
我认识他
I know him.
他在这里做什么
What the hell is he doing here?
我们来搞清楚
Let's find out.
麻烦多撒点彩糖
Extra sprinkles, please.
当然可以
Of course. Oh.
弥尔顿小姐的订单已经准备好了
I have the order ready for Ms. Milton.
请稍等
Just a moment.
给你
Here you go.
我加了最新口味的试吃  果仁糖之梦
I included samples of our newest flavor, Praline Dream.
不好意思
Excuse me.
那个不会是坚果巧克力口味吧
That wouldn't happen to be Rocky Road there, would it?
感谢您的耐心等待
Thank you for your patience.
没事
Yeah, no problem.
不用找了
And keep the change.
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thanks. - Thanks.
给你
Here you go.
不是黑树莓的  但你尝尝看怎么样
It's not black raspberry, but see what you think.
老天
Hot damn.
如果你不介意的话  我想说
If you don't mind me saying,
这个地方拥有各种各样的物质享受
this place has all kinds of creature comforts
我都不知道我有多想念这一切
I never knew how much I missed.
我是一个兴趣多多的人
I'm an interesting creature,
所以这对我来说是美好的一天
so this is a fine day for me.
对我来说也是非常美好的一天
Well, it's a very fine day for me, too.
我很高兴你来到这里
I'm glad you're here.
你在想什么  你走神了
Where are you? You drifted.
在我来的地方
A lot of people back where I'm from
有很多人需要这样一个地方
could use a place like this.
是的
Yeah.
尽管我愿意和你长相厮守
While I'd be content to keep strong with you indefinitely,
但如果我不完成来时的目标
I wouldn't be the man I am
我就不是我自己了
if I didn't do what I came here for.
我...
I, uh...
我们不能留下了
We can't stay.
我们得帮助我们的朋友们
We need to help our friends.
因为这里每个地方
Given the significant amount of red tape
都充满大量的繁琐程序
around every nook and cranny here,
我想知道有没有什么捷径可走
I was wondering if I could get some advice on how to cut through.
我希望我知道
I wish I had some,
但这里的一切真的都很慢节奏
but everything really moves slowly around here.
想坐坐吗
Want to sit?
镇上的无线电在那里面
The town radio is in there.
如果能和家里的人通话
I bet you'd feel better
我想你应该会好受一些
if you could talk to your people back home.
但你不敢问我
But you're afraid to ask.
我不想把你卷入
I'm afraid to involve you in something
你职责以外的事情
that's not your responsibility.
我想帮忙
I want to help.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我在通讯部门工作
I work in the Comms Department.
我可以使用设备
I could get access to the equipment,
但想要获得正式许可
but to get official clearance,
需要两周  所以...
it would take a couple weeks, so...
回到起点了
So back to square one.
我们找到了副监督员
We found the deputy supervisor.
她说想要见她领导需要五周
Says it'll be five weeks to see her boss.
也可能是好几年
Might as well be years.
你的提议有没有非正式版本
By any chance, is there an unofficial version of your offer?
天啊
Oh, wow.
妈妈说我们得待在这
Mom said we have to stay here.
谁干的
Who did this?
谁弄坏了手印板
Who broke our handprints?
-是你吗  -不是
- Was it you? - No.
不要撒谎
Don't lie.
你又要对我架刀子了吗
You gonna pull another knife on me?
我说了我没有
I said I didn't do it.
走了
Come on.
我可以帮你把它修好  朱迪思
I can help you put it back together, Judith.
我也可以
Me, too.
我们都可以
We all will.
我还记得你做这个的样子
I remember when you made those.
你当时那么小
You were so small.
卡尔希望你们有一段共同的回忆
Carl wanted you to have a memory together.
现在它坏了  他也走了
Now it's broken, and he's gone.
大家都走了
Everybody is.
我也很想他们
I miss them all, too.
会变得轻松吗
Does it get easier?
如果我说会  那就是在撒谎了
I'd be lying if I said it did.
我担心我会逐渐忘记他们
I'm worried I'll start to forget about them.
朱迪思
Judith.
其实我从没真正了解我爸
You know, I never really knew my dad.
我妈去世时
And my mom died when...
我比你现在大一点
I was a little older than you are now.
我仍经常想念她
I still miss her all the time.
我们相依为命了很长一段时间
For a long time, it was just the two of us.
经常搬家  换工作
And we moved a lot, from job to job.
但她总能让我们继续前进
But she always managed to keep us going.
我当时还不知道  但是
I didn't know it then, but...
她是在教我如何靠自己生存
she was teaching me to survive on my own.
哪天她要是不在了  我也能好好的
So I'd be okay if she ever wasn't there.
卡尔和你爸为你做了同样的事
And Carl and your dad did the same thing for you.
让你总能度过难关
So you'd always be able to get though the tough times.
木板固然不错
Pieces of wood are nice.
但你不需要这个来记住他们有多爱你
But you don't need that to remember how much they loved you.
再说  我很擅长修东西
Besides, I'm really good at fixing things.
你叫什么
Name?
别拿阿尔法或贝塔那种狗屁名字糊弄我们
And don't give us any of that Alpha/Beta garbage, either.
基斯
Keith.
我叫基斯
That's my name.
-你来这里干什么  基斯  -我没伤人
- What are you doing here, Keith? - I'm not hurting anyone.
回答问题
Just answer the question.
阿尔法死去后  人群四散而逃
A-After Alpha fell, the herd scattered.
那些没被杀死或烧死的都走了
Those who weren't killed or burned are gone.
只剩下我一个
I'm all that's left.
你没见过其他人
You haven't seen anyone else?
没有
No.
那你为什么留着尸群
Then why do you keep the walkers?
作为保护  慰藉
Protection, comfort.
旧习难改
Old habit.
你怎么想
What do you think?
我见过的低语者都是骗子
I think I haven't met a Whisperer who wasn't a liar.
那玛丽呢
What about Mary?
你就相信她
You believed her.
你怎么知道他在说谎
How do you know he's lying?
你凭什么确信他没说谎
What makes you so certain he isn't?
你有多了解他
How well do you know him?
他不是我母亲核心集团里的人
He wasn't part of my mother's inner circle.
他怕她
He was afraid of her.
那只能证明他有眼睛  仅此而已
Well, that proves he's got eyes, not much else.
莉迪亚
Lydia.
我在漫长的冬天曾趁阿尔法不注意
I snuck food to you during the long winters
偷送食物给你
when Alpha wasn't looking.
你还记得吗  告诉他们
You remember? Tell them.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
看来她并没有那么了解你
Guess she doesn't know you that well after all.
这无所谓
It doesn't matter.
我母亲死了  他没伤人
My mother's dead. He's not hurting anyone.
不  他有所隐瞒
No, he's hiding something.
你觉得是陷阱吗
You think it's a trap?
是也不奇怪
Wouldn't put it past him.
亚伦说得对  我们得确保他不是个威胁
Aaron's right. We need to make sure he's not a threat.
在我们决定如何处置他之前  先把他关进地窖
Let's get him into the cellar until we decide what to do with him.
不  不要
No. No!
-哥们  -怎么了
- Dude... - What is it?
不会是好事
Nothing good.
他不是一个人
He's not alone.
看看他还说了什么谎
Let's see what else he lied about.
还有多少人
How many more?
什么
What?
外面还有多少你们的人
How many more of you are out there?
就这些人  我发誓
This is it, I swear!
你以为我会相信吗
You expect me to believe that?
你刚刚才当着我面说谎
After you just lied to my face?
亚伦  你看他们
Aaron, look at them.
他们很害怕  只是想重新当人
They're scared. They're just trying to be people again.
他们也可能是威胁  藏在眼皮底下
Or they're a threat, hiding in plain sight
等待他们的人回来伏击我们
before their people come back and ambush us.
我们并不全是冷血怪物
We weren't all monsters.
求求你  求你了
Please. Please.
这是娜比拉的
This is Nabila's.
-杰瑞  -别说了
- Jerry... - No.
他们曾潜入亚历山大
They were in Alexandria.
烧毁了我们的家
They burnt down our home.
你想做什么
What do you wanna do?
当心
Look out!
轮到我了
My turn.
西二楼  法律部
北二楼  通讯部
西一楼  安保部
你既会使剑又会射箭吗
You're -- You're a swordswoman and an archer?
是的  必要时我还很擅长用弹弓
Yeah, I'm pretty good with a slingshot, too, in a pinch.
对一个律师来说很不错了
Not bad for a barrister.
你变化很大  由美子
Wow. You've changed, Miko.
你也是
So have you.
你怎么找到这地方的
How did you even find this place?
凯茜的万花筒
种子
灾变刚发生时  我逃离了芝加哥
I fled Chicago when things first started going bad.
我给你留了那通语音信息后
After I left you that voicemail,
就开车向东走
I got in a car and headed east.
在这里以北20英里的地方没油了
Ran out of gas about 20 miles north of here
但我很幸运  遇到了一些好人
but got lucky enough to link up with some good people.
我们很早就来到这里
We all wound up here pretty early on
那时弥尔顿一家刚把这里打造成避风港
when the Miltons made this place a safe haven.
一开始只是几个安全街区
It started with a few secure blocks,
但之后社区一点点地
but the community's been expanding
不断扩大
a little at a time ever since.
我几乎忘了
I, uh -- I almost forget
墙外的情况
what's going on outside these walls.
你一直以来就待在这里
And you've just been here this whole time,
做蛋糕吗
just making cakes?
我喜欢烘焙  那使我快乐
I like baking. It makes me happy.
-托米  你以前可是外科医生  -不
- Tomi, you were a surgeon. - Hey, no.
拜托  现在别说这个
Please, not now.
但你可以救死扶伤
But you could save people.
你还在试图操纵别人的生活吗  由美子
Still trying to run people's lives, Miko?
我没想挑事
I'm not trying to start anything.
我只想要你过好
I just want what's best for you.
你上次见我快乐是什么时候  由美子
When was the last time you saw me happy, Miko?
真正心满意足
Truly content?
记不起来了
Can't remember.
也许是现在吧
Maybe now.
我喜欢现在的生活
I like my life the way it is.
这是世界末日带给我的唯一礼物
It's the one gift I got out of the world falling apart.
拜托你别毁了这一切
Please, don't ruin this for me.
我当然不会了
Of course I wouldn't.
你只用告诉我一件事
Look, just tell me one thing.
这地方真有看起来那么好吗
Is this place really as good as it seems?
比那更好
Better.
如果我想替人求助的话  在这里可以做到吧
So if I wanted to get help for people, I could do that here?
一切皆有可能  只要你遵守规则
Anything's possible, as long as you follow the rules.
想吃蛋糕吗
Want some cake?
当然
Hell yes.
没想到会在这遇见你  默瑟
Fancy meeting you here, Mercer.
这地方显然有个健身房
Oh, they clearly got a gym in this joint.
你的身材真完美
Your chiseling is perfecto.
不好意思  我要进去办事
Uh, excuse me. Got business inside.
等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
我想感谢你
I... I wanted to thank you.
谢我什么
For what?
谢你把这个还给我
For making sure this got back to me.
不用谢
No need.
我只是把你的财物还给你  "公主"
Just returning your property, "Princess."
还有别的事吗
Was there something else?
有
Yeah.
你的睫毛美极了
You have really beautiful eyelashes.
告诉我其他人去哪了
Tell me where the others went.
他们在哪
Where are they?
还有多少人
How many more?
回答我
Answer me!
莉迪亚  救我  求你了
Lydia, help me! Please!
他们在哪
Where are they?!
阿尔法没看错你们
Alpha was right about you people.
你们假装自己高死人一等
You pretend you're better than the dead.
但死人很诚实
But dead is honest.
你们的朋友们死了更好
Your friends are better off.
你离死不远了
See, the clock's ticking now.
感觉更好了吗
Do you feel better off?
我可以帮你
Or I can help you.
我可以在感染扩散  你转变之前砍掉你的手
I can cut off your hand before the infection spreads and you turn.
你想要这样吗
Would you like that?
时间不多了
We don't have much time.
-求你了  -他们在哪
- Please... - Where are they?
我发誓我不知道  你一定要相信我
I don't know! I swear! You have to believe me...
低语者仍是个威胁吗
Are the Whisperers still a threat?
-不是  -别说谎
- No! - Stop lying!
-亚伦  够了  -不  我要答案
- Aaron, enough! - No, I need answers!
不  你要的是别的东西
No, you want something else.
我可不想在这里眼睁睁看着
I don't have to be here to watch it.
再来
Again.
说实话吧  哥们
Just tell the truth, man.
你想要我说什么
What do you want me to say?!
之前确实有更多人
There were more of us!
但他们都走了
But they -- they're gone!
我不知道
I don't know!
你他妈在做什么
What the hell are you doing?!
阻止你再做会后悔的事
Stopping you from doing something else you're gonna regret.
我在做必要的事  以保护每个我爱的人
I'm doing what I have to to keep everyone I love safe.
你最应该理解的
You of all people should understand that.
不该像这样做
Not like this.
看看周围
Look around.
我们正站在低语者
We are standing on the ashes
所毁掉的一切的灰烬上
of what the Whisperers destroyed.
正是因为他们  格雷西正在挨饿
Gracie is going hungry because of them!
这个世界充满了不可救药之人
The world is full of people who are beyond saving,
我可不想等着他们上门找我们
and I am not gonna wait for them to show up at our doorstep.
不
No.
亨利的遭遇...
What happened to Henry...
我之后的心情...
and how I felt after...
控制了我
it controlled me.
我任由自己走上了一条非常黑暗的道路
I let it take me down a very dark path.
我伤害了我在乎的人们
People that I care about were hurt.
现在不管我做什么  我都难以释怀
Now everything that I do, I carry that.
你不想走这条路的
This is a path you don't want to go down.
放他走吧
Now you let him go.
放他走
Let him go.
我可以砍掉你的手  你自己来也行
I can cut your hand off or you can do it yourself.
你选吧
Choice is yours.
好
Okay.
我说过我会找到的
Told you I'd find it.
这里吗
Right here?
亚历山大
Alexandria.
亚历山大  我是尤金  回话
Alexandria, this is Eugene. Come back.
尤金  尤金  你没事吧
Eugene! Eugene, are you okay?
罗西塔
Rosita?
听到你的声音太好了
Oh, it's dang good to hear your voice.
同感  朱迪思在我身边
You too. I got Judith here.
你好  你们都安全吗
Hi. Are you all safe?
你好  朱迪思
Hello! Hey, Judith.
是的  我们都安全  我们挺好的
Yes, we're all safe. We're doing okay.
那边情况如何
Uh, how are things there?
战争结束了
Well, the war's over.
阿尔法和贝塔死了
Uh, Alpha and Beta are dead.
但亚历山大一片狼藉  而且我们快没食物了
But... Alexandria's trashed, and we're running out of food.
对不起  我没听清...
I'm sorry. I didn't get --
尤金
Yeah. Eugene?
尤金  你还在吗
Eugene, are you still there?
尤金  你在哪
Eugene, where are you?
断了吗
Is he gone?
出故障了  没信号了
Something's haywire. Lost the feed.
试试高频
Uh, try a higher frequency.
手举起来  远离无线电
Hands up! Move away from the radio.
我保证我没造成任何损害
No harm's been done, I can assure you.
你被捕了
You're under arrest...
罪名是未经许可使用政府财产
...for the unauthorized use of government property.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
我要走了
I'm leaving.
不准拿走补给
Not with those supplies you aren't.
我要把它们带回亚历山大
I'm taking them back to Alexandria.
这个任务没有失败
This mission isn't finished.
对我来说失败了
It is for me.
住手
Stop it!
天啊  你们到了
Oh, my God. You made it.
你们还好吗
Are you okay?
更好更坏都经历过
Been better. Been worse.
我也是
Same.
我们在树林里遇到了彼此
We found each other in the woods.
确保了没人跟踪我们来这里
Made sure no one followed us back here.
很好  坐下
Good. Sit down.
我们不知道你是否还活着
We...didn't know if you'd survived.
但如果你活着  一定会在这里
But if you did, knew you'd be here.
其他人呢
What about the others?
邓肯  阿加莎  科尔  他们
Duncan, Agatha, Cole, they're --
他们死了
they're dead.
奥尔登
Alden's hurt.
他躲在一座教堂里
He's holed up in a church somewhere.
达里尔和弗罗斯特我不清楚
Daryl and Frost, I don't know.
那么
So then...
我们等
we wait.
We wait.
完蛋了
Holy shit.
我毁了一切
I've ruined everything.
我
I just...
和我一起在火车站的那个年轻女人呢
Where is the young woman that was with me at the train station?
特此通知  你们被控
You are hereby notified that you're being charged
肆意闯入  鲁莽危害
with wanton trespassing, reckless endangerment,
与外界组织非法通信
and illegal communication with a foreign entity --
全都是违反
all violations of Article 4,
《联邦刑法》第4条第2节的行为
Section 2 of the Commonwealth criminal code.
你们已获准在一小时内参加法官听证会
You've been granted a hearing before a judge within the hour.
如被判有罪  你们将被送到
If found guilty, you will be dropped off
远离城墙的区域  永久驱逐
in a zone far outside our walls and banished from ever returning.
我们这样做是有正当理由的
We did what we did for good reason.
如果你允许我们解释一下
If you'd just let us explain --
跟法官说去吧  虽然这没用
Tell it to the judge, although it won't matter,
因为你们来这里还不到一天
especially since you've been here less than a day
已经违反了好几条法律
and already broken several laws.
我们要和律师谈谈
We wanna talk to our lawyer.
你们有律师吗
You have an attorney?
当然有了  还是个厉害的律师
Damn right we do. A fancy one, too.
既然这地方痴迷于规矩
So if this place likes rules so much,
那你一定要允许我们找律师  这是我们的权利
you have to let us have one. It's our right.
公民才有权利
Rights are for citizens.
你们是寻求庇护者
You're asylum seekers.
特权是靠自己争取的
Privileges come when you've earned them.
拜托了
Please, just...
让我和史蒂芬妮谈谈
let me talk to Stephanie.
她可以为我们做担保
She can vouch for us.
她正在单独接受评估和指控
She's being processed and charged separately,
作为一个公民
as a citizen.
这太扯了
That's some bullshit.
交给我吧  约翰
I'll take it from here, John.
放他们走
Let them go.
霍恩斯比先生  我做不到  他们在候审
Mr. Hornsby, I can't. They're awaiting trial.
别碰他们
Do not move them.
我去找墨瑟
I'm going to find Mercer.
等等  他是不是那个
Wait. Was that...
俗气录像男
Cheesy video guy!
你们可以信任霍恩斯比
Hornsby is someone that you guys can trust.
谢谢
Thank you.
别急着谢我
Don't thank me so fast.
他也许能阻止你们被驱逐
He might be able to stop you from being banished,
但你们不会安然无恙
but it won't be scot-free.
你们仍要为所做的事付出代价
You'll have to pay for what you've done.
不论以哪种方式
One way or another.
对这一切我很抱歉
I'm sorry about all this.
我理解
I understand.
毕竟他的人失去了很多
After all his people have lost.
如果阿尔法还活着  她会做更糟糕的事
If Alpha were still here, she would've done worse.
给你的  蘑菇
For you -- mushrooms.
给你和其他人吃
For you and the others.
感谢你送我这个  还有你之前说的话
Thank you -- for this and for what you said.
我们不是都像她一样
We weren't all like her.
我们中有些人只是想生存
Some of us just wanted to survive.
永远别回头
Don't ever look back.
你不认为我们变了  对吗
You don't think we've changed, do you?
这我不好说
It's not for me to say.
我能证明
I can prove it.
-怎么证明  -我们见过你们的一个人
- How? - We saw one of your people.
从阿尔法的藏尸洞里逃出来的那个女孩
The girl who came out of the cave where Alpha kept the horde.
-你说什么  -在坍塌之后
- What did you say? - After the collapse.
本来有很多人
There were many,
后来成了两个人  最后只剩她了
then there were two, and then she was all alone.
-她没事吧  -她看起来受伤了  但还活着
- Was she all right? - She looked hurt but alive.
你最后一次见她是在哪里
Where did you last see her?
在树林里
In the woods.
在嚎叫山洞附近
By the screaming cave.
你怎么看
What do you think?
我觉得你没杀他可能是件好事
I'm thinking it's probably a good thing you didn't kill him.
你知道他所说的地方吗
Do you know where that is he's talking about?
我知道  在亚历山大附近
Yeah, yeah, it's near Alexandria.
-我们得立刻出发  -卡萝尔
- We gotta go...now. - Carol, Carol.
不  康妮还在外面活着
No. Connie's out there alive.
我知道  天色已晚
I know. It's getting late.
在我们回来前天会黑的
It'll be dark before we get back.
明天一早就去  好吗
Start at first light, yeah?